TUMININU ODUSANYA

CONTENT WRITER

LOCATION

Lagos, Nigeria

EMAIL

smattumi@gmail.com

PHONE NO.

+2347014635116

PORTFOLIO

00

LINKEDIN

LANGUAGES

English

TOOLS

Microsoft Word

Grammarly

Google Docs

Description of Air

PROFILE

Content writer with a knack for writing and publishing easily understandable and engaging content, with the ability to breakdown complex concepts, follow latest trends and deliver content on a diverse range of topics. Highly skilled in researching, proficeint in tech writing tools, and well-versed in SEO best practices and keyword placement. Currently open to opportunities to help gain meaningful experience and provide value. .

EXPERIENCE

Member Cowrywise Campus ambassador Content team (Unilag Chapter)

(January 2022 to date)

Worked with the rest of the team to create engaging, catchy and attention grabbing content in form of articles, broadcast messages, fliers and designs to promote **Cowrywise** in the University of Lagos

Money Africa Ambassador

(April 2022 to date)

Create content to market **Money Africa** to students and convert leads to customers.

NOTABLE PROJECTS

Understanding the world of NFT's

Introversion Vs Social anxiety

CERTIFICATES

SEO Training

EDUCATION

University of Lagos, Lagos, Nigeria

Bsc Zoology (Jan 2020-present)

SKILLS

Research Originality
Creative writing Adaptability
Search engine optimization (SEO) Proofreading

Knowledge of social media

Editing

Time Management

INTERESTS

Tech Storytelling
Finance Reading